<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style15.xsl"?>
<ancient_sites>
  <site>
    <name language="english">The Forbidden City</name>
    <location>4 Jingshan Front St, DongCheng, Beijing, China </location>
    <country>China</country>
    <description>
      The Forbidden City was the Chinese imperial palace from the Ming dynasty to the end of the Qing dynasty, the years 1420 to 1912. It is in the center of Beijing, China, and now houses the Palace Museum. It served as the home of emperors and their households as well as the ceremonial and political center of Chinese government for almost 500 years.
      Constructed from 1406 to 1420, the complex consists of 980 buildings and covers 72 ha (over 180 acres).The palace complex exemplifies traditional Chinese palatial architecture,and has influenced cultural and architectural developments in East Asia and elsewhere. The Forbidden City was declared a World Heritage Site in 1987,[4] and is listed by UNESCO as the largest collection of preserved ancient wooden structures in the world.
      Since 1925 the Forbidden City has been under the charge of the Palace Museum, whose extensive collection of artwork and artefacts were built upon the imperial collections of the Ming and Qing dynasties. Part of the museum's former collection is now in the National Palace Museum in Taipei. Both museums descend from the same institution, but were split after the Chinese Civil War. Since 2012, the Forbidden City has seen an average of 15 million visitors annually, and had 16 millions visitors in 2016.
    </description>
    <type>Imperial Palace, Art museum</type>
    <dimensions>
      <width type="original" unit="metre">961.00</width>
      <height type="original" unit="metre">754.00</height>
      <height type="current" unit="metre">752.00</height>

      <!-- <height type="current" unit="metre">138.75</height> -->
    </dimensions>
    <history>
      <dynasty>Ming to the end of the Qing</dynasty>
      <!-- <year>1420 to 1912</year> -->
      <year range="start" era="AD">1420</year>
      <year range="end" era="AD">1912</year>
    </history>

    <architect>Kuai Xiang</architect>
    <images>
        <!--<image size="thumb" type="jpg" url="https://cache-graphicslib.viator.com/graphicslib/thumbs674x446/2052/SITours/beijing-in-one-day-day-trip-from-shanghai-by-air-in-shanghai-107610.jpg">Forbidden City thumbnail</image>-->
		<image size="thumb" type="jpg" src="assets/images/forbiddingcity1.jpg">Forbidden City thumbnail</image>
        <image size="large" type="jpg" src="assets/images/forbiddingcity2.jpg">Forbidden City large</image>
        <image size="full" type="jpg" src="assets/images/forbiddingcity3.jpg">Forbidden City full</image>
    </images>
    <links>

        <overview type="general" url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Forbidden_City">wikipedia</overview>
    </links>
    <notes>
       <note type="intro">
      The Forbidden City is a rectangle, with 961 metres (3,153 ft) from north to south and 753 metres (2,470 ft) from east to west. It consists of 980 surviving buildings with 8,886 bays of rooms. A common myth states that there are 9,999 rooms including antechambers, based on oral tradition, and it is not supported by survey evidence. The Forbidden City was designed to be the centre of the ancient, walled city of Beijing. It is enclosed in a larger, walled area called the Imperial City. The Imperial City is, in turn, enclosed by the Inner City; to its south lies the Outer City.
    </note>
  </notes>

  </site>
  <site>
    <name language="english">Stonehenge</name>
    <location>Wiltshire</location>
    <country>England</country>
    <description>
        Stonehenge is a prehistoric monument in Wiltshire, England, 2 miles (3 km) west of Amesbury and 8 miles (13 km) north of Salisbury. It consists of a ring of standing stones, with each standing stone around 13 ft (4.1 metres) high, 6 ft 11 in (2.1 metres) wide and weighing around 25 tons. The stones are set within earthworks in the middle of the most dense complex of Neolithic and Bronze Age monuments in England, including several hundred burial mounds.
    </description>
    <type>Monument</type>
    <history>
      <dynasty>Old Kingdom</dynasty>
      <!-- <year era="BC">3000 to 2000</year> -->
      <year range="start" era="BC">3000</year>
      <year range="end" era="BC">2000</year>
    </history>

    <dimensions>
      <width type="average" unit="metre">2.1</width>
      <height type="original" unit="metre">4.2</height>
      <height type="current" unit="metre">4.0</height>
      <!-- <height type="current" unit="metre">138.75</height> -->
    </dimensions>

      <images>
        <image size="thumb" type="jpg" src="assets/images/Stonehenge1.jpg">Stonehenge thumbnail</image>
        <image size="large" type="jpg"  src="assets/images/Stonehenge2.jpg">Stonehenge large</image>
        <image size="full" type="jpg" src="assets/images/Stonehenge3.jpg">Stonehenge full</image>

       <!-- <img width="500" src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3c/Stonehenge2007_07_30.jpg">/ -->
    </images>


    <links>

        <overview type="general" url="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stonehenge">wikipedia</overview>
    </links>

    <notes>
       <note type="intro">
      One of the most famous landmarks in the UK, Stonehenge is regarded as a British cultural icon. It has been a legally protected Scheduled Ancient Monument since 1882 when legislation to protect historic monuments was first successfully introduced in Britain. The site and its surroundings were added to UNESCO's list of World Heritage Sites in 1986. Stonehenge is owned by the Crown and managed by English Heritage; the surrounding land is owned by the National Trust.
      </note>
    </notes>
  </site>


</ancient_sites>
